[
    {
      "question": "What is 1+1 ?",
      "options" : ["2", "3","4"],
      "isCorrect": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 3+1 ?",
      "options" : ["2", "3","4"],
      "isCorrect": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 5+4 ?",
      "options" : ["9", "12","8"],
      "isCorrect": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 9+1 ?",
      "options" : ["12", "11","10"],
      "isCorrect": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 10+12 ?",
      "options" : ["22", "23","24"],
      "isCorrect": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 13+33 ?",
      "options" : ["22", "53","46"],
      "isCorrect": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 53+7 ?",
      "options" : ["60", "59","61"],
      "isCorrect": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 82+10 ?",
      "options" : ["92", "83","94"],
      "isCorrect": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 94+37 ?",
      "options" : ["122", "143","141"],
      "isCorrect": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 222+44 ?",
      "options" : ["255", "266","222"],
      "isCorrect": 1
    }
  
]